

## **GAVIN RAINE R. DIZON**

## **Summary**

I am currently a student at De La Salle University Manila taking up Bachelor of Science in Computer Science (with specialization in Software Technology). I have already experienced programming in different languages such as Java, Python, and C. Furthermore, I have already experienced developing websites using HTML, PHP, CSS, and Javascript. I also make the design of some websites I have made.

## Education

(2)	Lourdes School Quezon City Primary and Secondary Education (Grade School, Junior High School, and Senior High School)	Jun 2006 - Apr 2019
<b>(2)</b>	De La Salle University (Manila)  Bachelor of Science in Computer Science with Specialization in Software Technology	Sep 2019 - Present
Work Experience		
$\bigoplus$	Poverello Online   An Online Research Database Full-Stacked Web Developer (PHP, SQL, CSS, HTML, & Javascript)   poverelloonline.lsqc.edu.ph	Oct 2018 - Jul 2019
$\bigoplus$	Pages and Beyond Full-Stacked Web Developer (PHP, SQL, CSS, HTML, & Javascript)   www.pagesandbeyond.com	May 2019 - Jul 2019
9	2nd LSQC Senior High School Research Colloquium Speaker/ Research Presenter	Jul 2019
$\bigoplus$	User Experience Philippines (UXPH) Front-End Web Developer (CSS, HTML, & Javascript)   www.uxph.org	Feb 2020 - present
Membership and Organizations		
De La Salle University User Experience Society  Member		2019 - present
Philippine Web Designers Organization (PWDO)  Member		2019 - present
Developer Students Club Taft (DSC Taft) Software Engineering Lead		2020 - present
User Experience Philippines (UXPH) Front-End Web Developer (Web Team)		2020 - present
Ckilla		

## Skills

**Graphic Design** 

Java, Python, and C

**Procedural and Object-Oriented Programming** 

Adobe Photoshop CS6/ CC

Web Development

Prototyping

HTML, PHP, mySQL, CSS, and Javascript (ES6)

Figma